

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# **PERSONAL PARTICULARS**

| Name                           | : | Sanitha C  |
|--------------------------------|---|--|
| Father's Name                  | : | Sasidharan C   |
| Gender                         | : | Female   |
| Date / Place of Birth          | : | 25 May 1988 / Kozhikode  |
| Age                            | : | 29 years   |
| Marital Status                 | : | Married  |
| Nationality/Religion           | : | Indian / Hindu   |
| Passport No.                   | : | Applied  |
| Height/ Weight                 | : | 159cm/ 62 kg   |
| Eye sight                      | : | 6/6  |
| Language Known                 | : | English, Malayalam & Tamil   |
| Present Residential<br>Address | : | Sanitha C Andathodath House Chalil Parambu North Beypore, Kozhikode Kerala – 673 015 Mobile - 9526593873 |
| Permanent Home<br>Address      | : | Sanitha C Andathodath House Chalil Parambu North Beypore, Kozhikode Kerala – 673 015 Mobile - 9526593873 |

Sanitha C

Mobile: +91-9526593873 sanithac1988@gmail.com

#### **Career Profile**

Well-organized and Highly creative professional in performing laboratory tests.

Produce reliable and precise observation data table to support experiments.

Experience of Applying Methodologies to carry out the Experiments.

Develop specimens and samples.

Expertise in operating standard laboratory equipment.

Experience of maintaining laboratory in well-stocked and resourced.

#### **Key Skills**

Knowledgeable in medical laboratory testing Proficient with patient sampling Amiable personality and has initiative Certified medical laboratory technician

#### HUMAN RELATION SKILLS:

Good interpersonal skills.

Self- Motivated.

Positive attitude towards life.

Hard working.

Speed with accuracy.

Talking Politely.

### **STRENGTHES**:

Punctual.

Presentational Skills.

Leadership Qualities.

Self-learning Attitude.

Self as well as team motivating personality.

Well organized and like to be neat with all of my work.

Hardworking individual, Quick learner and possess strong interpersonal skills.

# **Professional Experience**

### **Aroha Clinic**

Lab In Charge

February 2017- Till Date

Coordinate, setting-up and implement different services.

Supervise small group of technicians.

Collaborate and offer administrative assistance.

Perform routine laboratory functions.

Look after on chemical stock materials, cleaning equipment and laboratory instruments.

Programming, Calibrating Biochemistry & Hormone Analyzers

Perform & Maintain Data for EQA & IQA in Biochemistry & Immuno Assays.

### **Red Crescent Hospital**

Laboratory Technician

06<sup>th</sup> November 2015- 22<sup>nd</sup> January 2017

Coordinate in lab operations.

Conducting test and perform result analysis.

Prepare observation tables and record maintenance.

Programming Analyzers & Calibrating Parameters

Prepare chemicals before the practical session and assist students for finding the required chemical.

## Al Amal Hospital, Trippanachi, Manjeri Malappuram

Laboratory Technician

September 2015- October 2015

Assisted medical staff in performing tests for patients and for research purposes

Coordinate in lab operations.

Conducting test and perform result analysis.

Prepare observation tables and record maintenance.

Cash collection and Report on time submission

### National Lab & X Rays Ramanattukara, Kozhikode

Laboratory Technician

25<sup>th</sup> May 2013- 26<sup>th</sup> August 2015

Conduct hematological and seratological tests

Collect samples from patients requiring lab tests

Maintain the ;laboratory and equipment clean at all times

Supervise small group of junior lab technicians and lab interns

Prepare reports on results of tests for doctors' review and filing

#### Kalarickal X rays & Laboratory Ramanattukara, Kozhikode

Laboratory Technician

01<sup>st</sup> Feb 2009- 15<sup>th</sup> April 2015

Conduct hematological and seratological tests

Collect samples from patients requiring lab tests

Maintain the laboratory and equipment clean at all times

#### **Academic Qualifications**

Diploma in Medical Laboratory Technician from Kerala Medical Education Society in 2008 SSC from "Kerala Secondary Education Examination Board" 2006